# HAYDEN NEUMEYER

#### SUMMARY

Recent graduate proficient in Networking, Virtualization, and Microsoft Server Technologies pursuing a rewarding career in Information Technology utilizing my skills, talents, and experience to support the mission and professional effectiveness of any business or organization.

# CONTACT

- hayden@daemon.group
- A hadn69.com
- **4** 618 806 6912
- **♀** Seattle, WA

in hadn69 ♠ hadn69

## **EDUCATION**

Ranken Technical College

A.S. Computer Technology 2016

Southern Illinois University Edwardsville Computer Science

### **EXPERIENCE**

### Hadn69.com

PC Repair Technician

2015 to Current

Repair and build customer's personal PCs.

Tasks include:

Virus and malware removal Failed hardware replacement

Creating backups and transferring personal files

**Building custom PCs** 

#### Black Sun Network

Head Administrator / Owner

2012 to Current

Ensure smooth operation of all game servers, consistent communication with the community, and stability of all related services: website, Discord, IRC, and Mumble.

Recent achievements include:

Setting up automated backups

Deploying new server instances using docker Deploying a new web control panel for all services

# SIUE Solar Racing Team

Edwardsville, IL

Mechanical Director

2013 to 2014

In charge of all mechanical design, fabrication, and

implementation, including computer modeling and simulation.

Achievements in this position include:

Passing all safety checks during our first ever race

Performing finite element analysis to test the structure of the

frame design

Fabrication of structural reinforcement

#### **CERTIFICATIONS**

MCPS: Microsoft Certified Professional

MCTS: Windows 7, Configuration

CompTIA A+

#### **SKILLS**

Windows 7, Linux, Troubleshooting, Computer Hardware, Windows Server, Windows, Networking, Solar Energy, Matlab, Public Speaking, Programming, C++, PHP, Python